{"data":[{"question":"There's a lot of coffee, ______ there?","a":"aren't","b":"isn't","c":"hasn't","d":"doesn't","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"They'll tell you tomorrow, _______ they.","a":"won't","b":"tell","c":"will","d":"don't","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"They won't come yet, ______ they?","a":"won't","b":"will","c":"would","d":"do","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"She doesn't like tea, ______ she?","a":"does","b":"doesn't","c":"is","d":"has","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"They've got a dog, _______ they?","a":"haven't","b":"have","c":"do","d":"will","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"______ she?","a":"How old is","b":"How old has","c":"How many years is","d":"How many years has","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We use \" how old + Subject + to be \" when ask for age","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"You'll come with us, ______?","a":"will you","b":"you will","c":"won't you","d":"don't you","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+Positive statement, nagative tag? \n+ Nagative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"You don't speak German, _______ you?","a":"don't","b":"do","c":"speak","d":"can","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"You don't come every day, ______ you?","a":"do","b":"aren't","c":"don't","d":"doesn't","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"_______.","a":"How old is you?","b":"How many years have you?","c":"What years have you?","d":"How old are you?","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We use \" how old + Subject + to be \" when ask for age of someone","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}